{
  "miniGames": {
    "find_compositions": {
      "id": "find_compositions",
      "title": {
        "en": "Find Compositions"
      },
      "description": {
        "en": "Find all possible compositions for the target result"
      },
      "version": "1.0",
      "suggestedGradeRange": { "min": 2, "max": 5 },
      "defaultConfig": {
        "gradeConfig": {
          "2": { "max_number": 20, "min_number": 10, "num_questions": 5,  "min_required_answers": 3 },
          "3": { "max_number": 30, "min_number": 15, "num_questions": 6,  "min_required_answers": 4 },
          "4": { "max_number": 40, "min_number": 20, "num_questions": 7,  "min_required_answers": 5 },
          "5": { "max_number": 50, "min_number": 25, "num_questions": 8,  "min_required_answers": 6 }
        }
      }
    },
    "vertical_operations": {
      "id": "vertical_operations",
      "title": {
      "en": "Vertical Operations"
      },
      "description": {
      "en": "Solve vertical operations"
      },
      "version": "1.0",
      "suggestedGradeRange": { "min": 3, "max": 6 },
      "defaultConfig": {
        "gradeConfig": {
          "3": { "max_number": 100, "min_number": 50, "with_borrowing": false, "num_questions": 5,  "min_required_answers": 3 },
          "4": { "max_number": 500, "min_number": 200, "with_borrowing": true, "num_questions": 6,  "min_required_answers": 4 },
          "5": { "max_number": 999, "min_number": 500, "with_borrowing": true, "num_questions": 7,  "min_required_answers": 5 },
          "6": { "max_number": 999, "min_number": 500, "with_borrowing": true, "num_questions": 8,  "min_required_answers": 6 }
        }
      }
    },
    "multi_step_problem": {
  "id": "multi_step_problem",
  "title": {
  "en": "Multi-Step Word Problem"
  },
  "description": {
  "en": "Solve multi-step problems with multiple operations" },
  "version": "1.0",
  "suggestedGradeRange": { "min": 5, "max": 6 },
  "defaultConfig": {
    "gradeConfig": {
              "5":{
            "prompt_text": "",
            "num_questions": 2,
            "max_number": 200,
            "min_number": 100,
            "min_required_answers": 1   
          },
              "6": {
            "prompt_text": "",
            "num_questions": 2,
            "max_number": 300,
            "min_number": 150,
            "min_required_answers": 1
          }
          }
        }
      },
      "quick_multi_step_problem": {
      "id": "quick_multi_step_problem",
      "title": {
      "en": "Prepared Multi-Step Word Problem"
      },
      "description": {
      "en": "Solve multi-step problems with multiple operations" },
      "version": "1.0",
      "suggestedGradeRange": { "min": 5, "max": 6 },
      "defaultConfig": {
        "gradeConfig": {
                  "m_1":{
                            "prompt_text": "Ali had 120 marbles. He gave 20 to his brother, lost 15 on his way, and used 10 in a game.",
                            "num_questions": 3,
                            "max_number": 200,
                            "min_number": 100,
                            "min_required_answers": 1,
                            "steps": {
                                "0": {
                                    "question": "How many marbles does Ali have after giving 20 to his brother?",
                                    "answer": "100"
                                },
                                "1": {
                                    "question": "How many marbles does Ali have after losing 15 more?",
                                    "answer": "85"
                                },
                                "2": {
                                    "question": "How many marbles does Ali have after using 10 in a game?",
                                    "answer": "75"
                                }
                            }
                        },
                  "m_2":{
                        "prompt_text": "Sara had 150 stickers. She gave 30 to her friend, used 20 to decorate her notebook, and lost 10 on the way home.",
                        "num_questions": 3,
                        "max_number": 200,
                        "min_number": 100,
                        "min_required_answers": 1,
                        "steps": {
                            "0": {
                                    "question": "How many stickers does Sara have after giving 30 to her friend?",
                                    "answer": "120"
                            },
                            "1": {
                                "question": "How many stickers does Sara have after using 20 to decorate her notebook?",
                                "answer": "100"
                            },
                            "2": {
                                "question": "How many stickers does Sara have after losing 10 on the way home?",
                                "answer": "90"
                            }
                        }
                        }
                        ,
                  "m_3":{
                            "prompt_text": "Maya had 150 stickers. She gave 30 to her sister and 20 to her friend.",
                            "num_questions": 2,
                            "max_number": 200,
                            "min_number": 100,
                            "min_required_answers": 1,
                            "steps": {
                                "0": {
                                    "question": "How many stickers does Maya have after giving 30 to her sister?",
                                    "answer": "120"
                                },
                                "1": {
                                    "question": "How many stickers does Maya have after giving 20 to her friend?",
                                    "answer": "100"
                                }
                            }
                        },
                  "m_4":{
                            "prompt_text": "Omar had 200 dirhams. He spent 50 on books, 30 on a backpack, and 20 on lunch.",
                            "num_questions": 3,
                            "max_number": 200,
                            "min_number": 100,
                            "min_required_answers": 1,
                            "steps": {
                                "0": {
                                    "question": "How much does Omar have after buying books?",
                                    "answer": "150"
                                },
                                "1": {
                                    "question": "How much does Omar have after buying a backpack?",
                                    "answer": "120"
                                },
                                "2": {
                                    "question": "How much does Omar have after buying lunch?",
                                    "answer": "100"
                                }
                            }
                        },
                  "m_5": {
                            "prompt_text": "Salma had 100 pencils. She gave 25 to her classmates and lost 10.",
                            "num_questions": 2,
                            "max_number": 200,
                            "min_number": 100,
                            "min_required_answers": 1,
                            "steps": {
                                "0": {
                                    "question": "How many pencils does Salma have after giving 25 to her classmates?",
                                    "answer": "75"
                                },
                                "1": {
                                    "question": "How many pencils does Salma have after losing 10?",
                                    "answer": "65"
                                }
                            }
                        },
                  "m_6":{
                            "prompt_text": "Khalid had 180 points in a game. He lost 40 in the first round and 30 in the second.",
                            "num_questions": 2,
                            "max_number": 200,
                            "min_number": 100,
                            "min_required_answers": 1,
                            "steps": {
                                "0": {
                                    "question": "How many points does Khalid have after the first round?",
                                    "answer": "140"
                                },
                                "1": {
                                    "question": "How many points does Khalid have after the second round?",
                                    "answer": "110"
                                }
                            }
                        },
                  "m_7":{
                            "prompt_text": "Nadia had 160 dirhams. She spent 50 at the bookstore, then 40 at the caf\u00e9.",
                            "num_questions": 2,
                            "max_number": 200,
                            "min_number": 100,
                            "min_required_answers": 1,
                            "steps": {
                                "0": {
                                    "question": "How much does Nadia have after the bookstore?",
                                    "answer": "110"
                                },
                                "1": {
                                    "question": "How much does Nadia have after the caf\u00e9?",
                                    "answer": "70"
                                }
                            }
                        },
                  "m_8": {
                            "prompt_text": "Ali had 120 marbles. He gave 20 to his brother, lost 15 on his way, and used 10 in a game.",
                            "num_questions": 3,
                            "max_number": 200,
                            "min_number": 100,
                            "min_required_answers": 1,
                            "steps": {
                                "0": {
                                    "question": "How many marbles does Ali have after giving 20 to his brother?",
                                    "answer": "100"
                                },
                                "1": {
                                    "question": "How many marbles does Ali have after losing 15 more?",
                                    "answer": "85"
                                },
                                "2": {
                                    "question": "How many marbles does Ali have after using 10 in a game?",
                                    "answer": "75"
                                }
                            }
                        },
                        "m_9":{
                            "prompt_text": "Lina had 200 pages to read. She read 60 pages on Monday and 50 on Tuesday.",
                            "num_questions": 2,
                            "max_number": 200,
                            "min_number": 100,
                            "min_required_answers": 1,
                            "steps": {
                                "0": {
                                    "question": "How many pages does Lina have left after Monday?",
                                    "answer": "140"
                                },
                                "1": {
                                    "question": "How many pages does Lina have left after Tuesday?",
                                    "answer": "90"
                                }
                            }
                        },
                        "m_10":{
                            "prompt_text": "Sara had 160 beads. She used 40 for a bracelet, 30 for a necklace, and 10 fell and were lost.",
                            "num_questions": 3,
                            "max_number": 200,
                            "min_number": 100,
                            "min_required_answers": 1,
                            "steps": {
                                "0": {
                                    "question": "How many beads are left after using 40 for a bracelet?",
                                    "answer": "120"
                                },
                                "1": {
                                    "question": "How many beads are left after using 30 for a necklace?",
                                    "answer": "90"
                                },
                                "2": {
                                    "question": "How many beads are left after losing 10 beads?",
                                    "answer": "80"
                                }
                            }
                        },
                        "m_11":{
                            "prompt_text": "Iliass had 200 coins. He spent 40 on candy, 30 on a toy, gave 20 to a friend, and lost 10 on the street.",
                            "num_questions": 4,
                            "max_number": 200,
                            "min_number": 100,
                            "min_required_answers": 1,
                            "steps": {
                                "0": {
                                    "question": "How many coins are left after buying candy?",
                                    "answer": "160"
                                },
                                "1": {
                                    "question": "How many coins are left after buying the toy?",
                                    "answer": "130"
                                },
                                "2": {
                                    "question": "How many coins are left after giving 20 to a friend?",
                                    "answer": "110"
                                },
                                "3": {
                                    "question": "How many coins are left after losing 10 on the street?",
                                    "answer": "100"
                                }
                            }
                        },
                        "m_12":{
                            "prompt_text": "Yasmine had 190 pens. She gave 40 to her classmates, 30 to her teacher, used 10 herself, and dropped 10 on the ground.",
                            "num_questions": 4,
                            "max_number": 200,
                            "min_number": 100,
                            "min_required_answers": 1,
                            "steps": {
                                "0": {
                                    "question": "How many pens are left after giving 40 to classmates?",
                                    "answer": "150"
                                },
                                "1": {
                                    "question": "How many pens are left after giving 30 to her teacher?",
                                    "answer": "120"
                                },
                                "2": {
                                    "question": "How many pens are left after using 10 herself?",
                                    "answer": "110"
                                },
                                "3": {
                                    "question": "How many pens are left after dropping 10 on the ground?",
                                    "answer": "100"
                                }
                            }
                        },
                        "m_13":{
                            "prompt_text": "Rania had 170 apples. She sold 50 at the market, 40 to a neighbor, gave 10 to her cousin, and threw away 10 that were bad.",
                            "num_questions": 4,
                            "max_number": 200,
                            "min_number": 100,
                            "min_required_answers": 1,
                            "steps": {
                                "0": {
                                    "question": "How many apples are left after selling 50 at the market?",
                                    "answer": "120"
                                },
                                "1": {
                                    "question": "How many apples are left after selling 40 to a neighbor?",
                                    "answer": "80"
                                },
                                "2": {
                                    "question": "How many apples are left after giving 10 to her cousin?",
                                    "answer": "70"
                                },
                                "3": {
                                    "question": "How many apples are left after throwing away 10 bad ones?",
                                    "answer": "60"
                                }
                            }
                        }
              }
            }
          }

    }
  }
           